So Robin is in that
building behind you, huh?
Out of my way, bull guy!
Listen, boy.
Perhaps you haven't realized this,
but what you're doing right now is
nothing short of a world-class crime.
Let's go.
I'll see
you
next time.
We won't go around the world!
Start me up.
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
All right now, I'll
show you all in my heart
The new world, stop me up!
Stupid bastards!
Oh.
Oh, I see.
Understood. So then,
when Sodom and his brother Gomorrah were
about to die in the belly of a sea king,
the Franky family showed up.
They were rescued and told these
fateful words that he still remembers.
Look, we're already full
so we're not gonna eat you.
And from that day forward,
the two brothers swore their
undying loyalty to their savior,
Franky.
So let me get this straight.
The Franky family brought down a sea king,
ate it, and they just
happened to be saved?
because Franky was already full?
Pretty much.
Fine, whatever.
You mind watching where you're going?
You're making me nervous.
I will follow big bro Franky
until the day I die, he says.
I bet he's really happy that one of
us can understand what he's saying.
He said, by the way,
the masked guy that was with you
never made it on board my back.
Is that OK?
Ah!
He's talking about Sniper King!
Where is he?
Why now? Why now?
Idiot.
The fall off?
Did you hear?
He hasn't been here from the start!
Don't tell me.
Did he run away again?
Arrogant pirates, you can't keep
this foolishness up forever!
If you want to pass, you'll
have to go through me to do it.
Fine then!
Is that really the best you've got?
Battleship cannon!
Come on!
There's only three of them!
Do something!
So, you're good at fighting, aren't you?
Then you can beat those guys, huh?
You bet.
We'll get her back.
We just needed motivation.
Now that we know Robin needs saving,
there's no limit to what Luffy and
the rest of our crew can accomplish.
I believe in him.
He can do it.
Go!
Get that rope guy!
Not gonna happen.
Shrouds and Ratlander!
We're gone far!
Consider this a dead end.
Give up and go.
Just get to the point already.
The power of the world government
stretches across more than 170 nations.
This island is a symbol of
our strength and resolve.
Attacking it is not simply
an act of rebellion,
but a declaration of war against
every country in our alliance.
We are bound by our
honor to strike you down.
You will not only face a merciless death,
but serve as an example
to the entire world.
You're at most a few dozen men.
You should have thought
this out more carefully.
I said out of my way!
So are you going to move or what?
It doesn't matter if I move or not.
The point is that you
condemned yourself to a death
sentence the second you
set foot on Endy's lobby.
You understand that?
Fighting is a waste of time.
You got a taste of our
strength at Iceberg's Mansion.
You cannot defeat our six powers.
The difference between
us is simply too great.
Yeah, maybe that's true.
But you know, for some reason, I have
a feeling I'm gonna win this time.
Here we go!
Iron Buddy.
Kum Kum Rifle!
This doesn't make any sense.
He wasn't like this at all
when I fought him before.
How is it that he's so much stronger now?
Goblin!
Chase!
I don't care about your honor or
your government or any of that.
You do what you want with that crap.
All that matters is
getting Robin out of here.
What are we going to do?
It's too late now.
Even if we wanted to, it's not like
we could go back and pick him up.
I'm sure he'll figure
out something or other.
But the whole island is
swarming with Marines.
He's not Luffy, after all.
He can't fight them off on his own.
Even if we don't realize it at first,
we've gotten stronger with
every challenge we've faced.
You may not think he's tough, but
he's survived as well as anyone else.
No one from our crew would die
at a time like this. Don't worry.
Look!
We're almost to the courthouse!
This ought to stop them.
We've been hit! No!
Hold back!
We finally got one!
Sodom!
No!
This is bad!
He needs my help!
Rip those teeth and hold on, Sodom!
You can't fall yet!
Guys!
You're gonna have to jump!
Get off it quick!
Sodom can't go on!
That mortar hit him square in the chest!
He's about to go down!
You gotta keep moving no matter what!
You're the only ones who can do this!
He says go!
He's coming down!
Nobody's riding it!
Where'd they go?
Come on.
Let's go, Gomorrah!
Why'd I have to not
land on that King Bull?
What am I going to do?
I'm way behind everyone else now.
These shipwrights are awesome, but I
should probably catch up with the others.
Then again, I did leave
the crew, didn't I?
Maybe I should just run away.
No!
Running is the last thing I should do!
It doesn't matter whether I'm
a part of the crew or not.
I put on this disguise
so I can help my friends.
If Robin is willing to sacrifice herself
to save us, it's the least I can do.
My manhood's on the line here!
All right.
There's only one way to get back
to the others at this point.
I call it operation disguise
myself as one of the government
agents and walk straight to the
courthouse without anyone noticing.
Okay, let's do this.
Enemy attack!
They're flooding the island!
We're all gonna sink!
The giant woke up!
We tried for 50 years to pull it.
We let up on the town.
You mean the government?
We're distressed to all
the giants in Elbath.
Elbath? Giants? Bosses?
Wait a sec.
Are you saying you're from Elbath?
Like the Warriors Village Elbath?
Who the hell are you, runt?
I'm Sniper King from Sniper Island.
I'm interested in your story.
By all means, continue.
Take your time.
There's not much point in telling
you, but I guess it can't hurt.
Kashi and I used to be
pirates a hundred years ago.
Our crew traveled the whole world.
But everything changed when
we visited a certain island.
Since they couldn't come to an
agreement, our two bosses started a duel.
We had to split up the crew.
We were at a loss.
All we could do was go
back to our hometowns.
A warrior's battle is life or death.
But as soon as it's over, the winner is
supposed to come back to their village.
We waited for 50 years and
never heard from either of them.
Something was wrong.
So Kashi and I set out
to sea to go back to the
island and find out what
happened with the duel.
But on our way there, we got
captured by some marines.
They forced us to answer all
kinds of questions about our crew.
Then we found out the truth.
Even though our bosses
were strong fighters,
they got caught by marines just like us
and were stuck in some big government jail.
All of that stuff happened
about 50 years ago.
The government made a deal with us.
They said if we would work for them for
100 years, they'd set our bosses free.
All we had to do was protect
and escape from intruders.
As long as we didn't let anyone through,
when our time was up, our bosses and
us could all go back to Elbaf together.
Since China's lived to be 300 or
so, we didn't think it was so bad.
So we agreed to the deal and kept
all of the bargain for 50 years.
But then those pirates came through
the gate and ruined everything.
That's why I'm so ashamed.
That's why I'm crying.
It's not fair.
Now our bosses are gonna be stuck in that
dumb prison for the rest of their lives.
Hey, hold on. Wait a second.
There's something funny about that story.
You think this is funny, you little jerk?
How dare you laugh at our pride?
I don't mean like funny
ha-ha, I mean funny weird.
Hey, what's so weird about it?
Before we came here,
my crew met those bosses of yours,
and we saw them fighting their duel.
Their names are Dorry and Broggy, right?
The warriors from Elbath, fighting
in an evenly matched duel,
over and over again, for a hundred years.
How do you know their names?
You must be lying.
If you need more proof than that,
I can tell you anything you want.
And then...
You still don't believe me?
What do I have to tell you?
They're weapons, maybe?
How they fight?
73,466 duels!
I know everything about them!
We really met them!
I swear it!
They weren't captured 50 years ago!
That's nothing but a big fat lie!
It's coming! Wait! Aim carefully!
Get it in your sights, men!
It's a trench mortar!
Gomorrah, dodge!
Damn, bastards had an ammo.
waiting for us.
Taking the main road sure was a bad idea.
Turn around, quick!
Not so fast!
Sorry, son of...
Stop right there!
Chopper.
Who could be calling?
Yes? Hello?
Howdy, howdy! Granny Kaku!
What's going on?
Alright, sounds like you're still alive.
There's a little something
I forgot to tell you.
I'm sure you're busy,
so I'll make it quick.
Listen carefully.
If you remember that map Polly drew,
you might notice there's no path from the
courthouse to the gates
of justice that's been.
bothering me but i was
afraid to ask about it look
at the courthouse you see
those towers on either.
side yeah i see them
all right now there's a
lever on the top floor
of each of those towers.
if you folks can get in there and pull
both of them a drawbridge will come
down from the courthouse to the gates
of justice whoa but how do you know
about all that stuff granny i came here
with tom ages ago to fix that bridge
damn stupid ungrateful government
don't take it out on me chimney wants
to talk too pirate lady hey can you hear
me hello i've got you loud and clear
guess what i just saw your rubber
pirate buddy he was over on the rooftop
of the courthouse just now yeah yeah
so that's where he is there was a
bunch of smoke and broken stuff up there
too so it looks like he's wrecking.
the place.
Thanks.
Hopefully we'll get there soon.
And by the way, don't
hang up the transponder
snail.
I'd like to keep track of
what's going on with you folks.
No problem. See ya.
Can't keep the
captain waiting, right men?
Good.
You head straight for the courthouse.
The sooner that your crew can The
more we get back together, the better,
that's what I say.
Sounds good.
Meanwhile, we'll split into two
groups and bring down the drawbridge.
You hear that, Gomorrah?
To the courthouse!
Gomorrah!
Damn, who the hell is that?
Don't get too cocky, scumbags.
All right the second one's down two
How's that huh?
Not so fast now, are you?
Everybody move in! Attention!
All marine guards here in block
D in the southeast quadrant
the virus king bull has been
eliminated all units should
move in immediately form a
blockade around the entire area
I repeat all military personnel
surround Unblock D now!
Seems that the jurymen have
delivered the verdict for us.
And it's guilty as usual, huh?
Hmm.
Say something, man! Sir!
Yes, sir, on our way! Yeah!
The Marines we trampled over
are catching up to us again.
Not good.
And it's not just them!
We're surrounded here!
We've got trench borders aimed at us, too!
Ahhhh!
There's gotta be like a million
bajillion of those guys out there!
We can't even run away anymore!
What are we gonna do?!
Damn, you got it good.
Not everyone gets their own rescue squad.
Well, just saying.
It's not like I'm bitter because
my men aren't coming to save me.
They got better stuff to do, I'm sure.
Ah, that's right.
I almost forgot.
Before you leave, you
should take these with you.
Wait a sec!
Those are devil fruits, aren't they?
Yo-yo! My!
What a surprise!
Cha-bum-bum!
I've never seen one in person before!
It's my first time as
well! Gah! Stay away!
Don't let those things near me!
You ate one too.
What's your problem?
Why the fuss? What?
Haven't you heard?
The reason they're called devil
fruits is because the people
who eat them have a little devil
living inside their bodies.
Just think,
if I get too close to one of those things,
the devil inside me
might pop out and start
fighting with the devil inside the fruit.
If that happens, my whole
body will be blown to bits.
You're kidding me.
That's nonsense.
You're a member of an intelligence agency,
and you believe that? What a shame.
The condition for the transfer
of Devil Fruit powers has been
confirmed by scientists on the
Grand Line for quite some time.
The condition you're talking about only
happens when someone eats two devil fruits.
I don't know if devils are involved,
but their bodies do burst apart.
The price for greed. What fools.
If you think about the risk that
comes with eating one fruit,
you can only imagine
what kind of disaster you
might bring upon yourself
by eating two of them.
Huh.
So that's how it works.
Still, I'm surprised.
I can't believe you got two of these.
Pretty impressive, Chief.
How'd you pull that one?
Let's just say I have
connections, how's that?
At any rate, best of luck.
That's right, Cape.
Grow stronger and stronger.
As always, there is a
certain risk involved.
We don't know what kind of
devils reside in those fruits.
I've never seen a fruit like
this in any reference book.
You can feel a strange power coming
from them, a heaviness in the air.
It's like they're from a different world.
That's what everyone says.
I've been told that you only learn the name
of the fruit once you absorb its powers.
But there's no guessing what
kind of ability you'll gain.
Well, there's no denying
that there's a risk involved.
The wrong power could ruin your life.
And either way, you'll no
longer be able to swim.
It's not an issue of what power
you get, but how you use it.
No matter what, you won't get weaker.
And as for being unable to
swim, it's hardly a problem.
It's a rare treasure of the
thousands who search for them.
I'm sure most end up empty-handed
or dead by the end of their journey.
Just try it already.
It'll be interesting.
Don't do it! Are you crazy?
That thing's evil!
Also, they taste like crap, I tell you!
Crap! Yeah, right. He's jealous.
He doesn't want them getting
stronger, Jabba-Bah. Shame!
You should know, Jabra, that envy
and resentment are a man's downfall!
Yo-yo-ee!
Hey, shut up!
Come on, just stop.
Think about this.
If you sell these things,
you could make millions.
But one bite and you'll be
cursed for the rest of your life.
Yep, interesting, all right.
Here goes. Hope it's good.
Ah, they ate them! No!
Cha-pa-pa!
What's wrong?
Is your body besieged with
a strange metamorphosis?
Cha-pa-pa!
Gross.
Stay so stoner!
It's really gross.
Yeah, we got that, Chubbaba!
And yet, you ate the whole
thing without a word!
Well, come on, try
doing something already.
I want to see what kind of powers you got.
I don't realize if anything is different.
Soon, you'll understand
the extent of your changes.
The birth of new Devil Fruit
users is always exciting.
Enjoy yourselves.
But I'd try to get those powers
under control while you still can.
Depending on our orders might have
to use them in real combat soon?
It seems Bluno couldn't wait.
We'll have to see if
he saves any fun for us
All right!
Raimo and Kashi are back on their feet!
We're screwed.
I don't have the strength to
fight these guys a second time.
We were so close!
Crush those criminals into the ground!
Grind their little bones
between your toes, Giants!
You bastards!
How dare you!
Lie to us!
What the hell?
Don't tell me they betrayed us!
And now, with our bossy safe, Before
we mourn all those years we wasted,
we're going to let out every
last ounce of our anger on you.
Are you ready, King of the Snipers?
Let us not waste words!
Voice the signal for the counterattack!
Soon we shall be reunited
with our comrades!
You're not bad.
Not bad.
I never thought he'd be able to
keep up with the speed of shave.
I'll have to watch that.
And since he's made of rubber,
direct attacks won't work.
Moonwalk.
Now come come.
Tempest King.
Iron body.
Wheel.
Door door.
Was that a door on the ground?
Door door
Whoa, wait a sec, now there's a bunch
of little ones all over the place too!
Damn it, I can't move! This sucks!
It's a stupid trap!
You're the one doing this! But how?
A Devil Fruit?
The door door fruit, naturally.
I turn all that I touch into door.
Revolving door.
Oh, what?
I'm not moving anywhere, but I'm spinning.
I don't know which way is front.
Make it stop.
Tempest kick.
Cook, see that?
Yeah, I saw.
You know what that means.
Luffy's already fighting CP9.
What? Huh? Seriously? Damn it!
We're too late!
But there's nothing we can do!
We're totally surrounded!
And after taking that last big hit, I
don't think Gamora's going anywhere!
Everyone open fire and shoot those pirates
down from the monster
before it gets back up!
Look, we gotta run.
We can't wait here any longer.
Yeah, let's cut through to the courthouse.
It's our only option.
Right, let's go! Are you ready? Yeah!
Wait!
Nobody get up!
What? Why?
Everyone, hold on tight!
That's what Cobra says!
It's still alive!
The monster's getting back up!
Fire!
Stop it with the Trenchporter!
Take that thing down!
Return fire! Come on! Hurry!
Go, Gomorrah! Charge!
I wasn't looking for a dream.
In a light for me.
I put a light back.
I was going tomalay.
I don't want to leave.
After every day I'm asleep?
How many times, how many
times, I'm standing by?
I'm looking at my smile and my tears.
How many times in the dark,
I'll be sure that tomorrow will come.